<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- produced for the bleb.org TV system at Thu Feb 18 08:39:02 2016 -->
<channel id="bbc1" source="XMLTV" date="18/02/2016">
  <programme>
<start>0600</start>
<end>0915</end>
<title>Breakfast</title>
<desc>The latest news, sport, business and weather from the BBC's Breakfast team. Also in HD. [S] Including regional news at 25 and 55 minutes past each hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1000</end>
<start>0915</start>
<desc>19/20. Consumer programme. Matt Allwright meets a single mum who is struggling to cope after a dispute with her landlord. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<title>The Housing Enforcers</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1000</start>
<end>1100</end>
<desc>Property renovation series. Martin, Lucy and Dion visit projects in Crewe in Cheshire, Chartham Hatch in Kent and Rusholme in Manchester to hear their buyers' money-making plans. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<title>Homes Under the Hammer</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1100</start>
<end>1145</end>
<title>Wanted Down Under Revisited</title>
<desc>10/16. Randle Family: Two years after a trial week in Australia, have the Randle family moved there for good? Also in HD. [S]</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>1215</end>
<start>1145</start>
<desc>4/10. Series which sees insurance fraudsters caught on camera. Secret filming and a musical performance are instrumental in catching out a postman making a personal-injury claim. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<title>Claimed and Shamed</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Bargain Hunt</title>
<desc>Oswestry Showground plays host to two more teams of bargain hunters. Tim Wonnacott visits Wightwick Manor in Wolverhampton to explore an arts and crafts masterpiece. Also in HD. [AD,S]</desc>
<subtitle>Oswestry</subtitle>
<end>1300</end>
<start>1215</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>The latest national and international news stories from the BBC News team, followed by weather. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<title>BBC News at One</title>
<end>1330</end>
<start>1300</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>The latest news, sport and weather from London. [S]</desc>
<title>BBC London News</title>
<end>1345</end>
<start>1330</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Being Witched</subtitle>
<desc>Mrs Tembe makes a life-changing decision. Also in HD. [AD,S]</desc>
<title>Doctors</title>
<start>1345</start>
<end>1415</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>14/15. The Deadly Seal: Father Brown is told that Bishop Talbot will be assassinated. Also in HD. [AD,S]</desc>
<title>Father Brown</title>
<end>1500</end>
<start>1415</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Buyers are helped to find their dream homes. Alistair Appleton rises to the challenge in Shropshire, as he helps a husband and wife with a unique house-hunting technique. Also in HD. [AD,S]</desc>
<title>Escape to the Country</title>
<end>1545</end>
<start>1500</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>...Goodman. 14/25. Len Goodman takes TV personality, author and former MP Edwina Currie to sunny Bournemouth to relive her childhood holiday of 1957. Also in HD. [AD,S]</desc>
<title>Holiday of My Lifetime with Len...</title>
<start>1545</start>
<end>1630</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1630</start>
<end>1715</end>
<subtitle>Gloucester</subtitle>
<title>Flog It!</title>
<desc>Antiques series. The team are in Gloucester, where presenter Paul Martin and experts Philip Serrell and Michael Baggott discover some rare gems. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Quiz in which contestants try to score as few points as possible by plumbing the depths of their general knowledge to come up with the answers no-one else can think of. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<title>Pointless</title>
<start>1715</start>
<end>1800</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>BBC News at Six</title>
<desc>The latest national and international news stories from the BBC News team, followed by weather. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<end>1830</end>
<start>1800</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>The latest news, sport and weather from London. [S]</desc>
<title>BBC London News</title>
<start>1830</start>
<end>1900</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>If it's got Britain talking then it will get talked about on The One Show. Presented by Matt Baker and Alex Jones. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<title>The One Show</title>
<start>1900</start>
<end>1930</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>1930</start>
<end>2000</end>
<desc>Tina shares her concerns with Sonia about their relationship. Martin reaches breaking point, and Abi begins to have doubts. Also in HD. [AD,S] Then BBC News.</desc>
<title>EastEnders</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>18/20. Bucket begins the unpleasant task of bringing the murderer to justice. Also in HD. [AD,S]</desc>
<title>Dickensian</title>
<end>2030</end>
<start>2000</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Room 101</title>
<desc>5/9. Frank Skinner hosts as Shaun Ryder, Meera Syal and Australian comedian Sam Simmons compete to have their pet hates consigned to Room 101. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<end>2100</end>
<start>2030</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>2100</start>
<end>2200</end>
<desc>7/8. Detective drama series. When a marine salvage hunter is killed, the evidence seems to point to one man. The trouble for the team is that the suspect has a solid alibi. Also in HD. [AD,S]</desc>
<title>Death in Paradise</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>2200</start>
<end>2230</end>
<title>BBC News at Ten</title>
<desc>The latest national and international news, with reports from BBC correspondents worldwide. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>BBC London News</title>
<desc>The latest news, sport and weather from London. [S] Followed by national weather.</desc>
<start>2230</start>
<end>2245</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<end>2345</end>
<start>2245</start>
<title>Question Time</title>
<desc>David Dimbleby presents from Stratford-upon-Avon. Panellists include Justine Greening, Lisa Nandy, John Nicolson, June Sarpong and Theo Paphitis. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>2345</start>
<end>0045</end>
<title>Professor Green: Suicide and Me</title>
<desc>Rapper Professor Green takes an intensely personal journey to uncover the truth behind the suicide of his father. Contains some strong language.  Also in HD. [S]</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<start>0045</start>
<end>0050</end>
<desc>Detailed weather forecast. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<title>Weather for the Week Ahead</title>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>BBC One joins the BBC's rolling news channel for a night of news, with bulletins on the hour and the headlines every 15 minutes. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<title>BBC News</title>
<start>0050</start>
<end>0600</end>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<title>Breakfast</title>
<desc>The latest news, sport, business and weather from the BBC's Breakfast team. Also in HD. [S] Including regional news at 25 and 55 minutes past each hour.</desc>
<end>0915</end>
<start>0600</start>
  </programme>
</channel>
